<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EventMe</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">MG Labs</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">mglabs@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <integer-array name="event_ID">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="event_titles">
        <item>Meeting Point</item>
        <item>Il Festival del panino</item>
        <item>Tesori d&apos;Oriente</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="event_info">
        <item>Malta è ufficialmente l&quot;isola del Blockchain.
                E' il primo paese europeo ad aver creato un framework legislativo dedicato alla Blockchain e alle Crypto valute.
            Questo rappresenta una pietra miliare per tutta il comparto legato a questa teconologia e a tutto il settore Fintech.
            Durante l'Italian Blockchain Summit approfondiremo tutta la normativa maltese attraverso
            l'analisi dei maggiori esperti nel settore.
            Ci sarà la possibilità di affrontare casi concreti di imprenditori italiani che hanno già realizzato
            delle ICO e verificare alcune criticità.</item>
        <item>I panini, come potete ben immaginare, sono dalla prima edizione i veri protagonisti
            delle serate; sono conditi con i companatici tipici della tradizione della conservazione
            delle ortive locali e dei prodotti dell’Adriatico sottolio e sottaceto. Sono proposti
            in tante gustosissime varianti, con pomodori sott’olio, melanzane, frittata, carciofi,
            peperoni, lampascioni, acciughe, tonno, ricotta forte e parmigiana.</item>
        <item>Il 25-26-27-28 Aprile e 1-4-5 Maggio 2019, il Festival dell’Oriente torna a Roma,
            presso la Nuova fiera di Roma, nel contesto dell’evento “Roma incontra il Mondo”
            composto da tanti altri Festival.
Mostre fotografiche, bazar, stand commerciali, gastronomia tipica, cerimonie tradizionali,
            spettacoli folklorisitici, medicine naturali, concerti, danze e arti marziali
            si alterneranno nelle numerose aree tematiche dedicate ai vari paesi in un continuo ed
            avvincente susseguirsi di show, incontri, seminari ed esibizioni..</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="event_images">
        <item>@drawable/img_event3</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_event2</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_event1</item>
    </array>

    <string name="title_activity_detail">DetailActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="event_not_found">Event Not Found</string>

</resources>
